CURRICULUM VITAE

06/09/2019

Personal information

Name: Kenneth Ochieng Adodi

Phone number: 0711494107

Email address: Kennethadodi@gmail.com

Address: 2642, Kakamega.

Objectives

To be top-class professional in my field of specialization

To learn as much as possible from academic and corporate personnel so as to achieve competence in the earliest possible time

To be an individual that adds value to both my country's economy and the organization I work for.

Education

2010 to 2015

Kenyatta University, BScs Electrical and Electronics Engineering

I graduated with a Second Class – Upper Divison

2005-2008

Kakamega High School

I attained a mean grade of A- MINUS(A-), getting a total of 80 points out of a possible 84 points in my Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education(K.C.S.E) exam.

1997-2004

Amalemba Primary School

I got 420 marks out of a possible 500 marks in my Kenya Certificate of Primary Education (K.C.P.E) exam.

Experience

2018 – Present: Electrical Engineer (Building Services) at the State Department of Public Works

2017 – 2018: Lecturer (Electrical and Electronics Engineering) at Trident Colleges

2015 – 2017: Junior Electrical Engineer at Superfoam Mattresses Limited

2013 May-August: Internship at Kenya Power Company.

2014 May-August: Internship at Kenya Electricity Transmission Company (KETRACO)

Additional Training

2014 September – November: Student Training for Entrepreneurial Promotion (STEP), training from University of Luneburg (Leuphana) and UNESCO in association with Kenyatta University

Hobbies

Playing basketball

Reading novels and scientific journals

Traveling

Skills

- Good knowledge of the computer including a deeper understanding of both the hardware and software elements
- Basic knowledge in computer programming (C++ language)

Strength

- First learner
- Team player
- A good listener
- Social
- All-round individual

Referees

1. Vincent Keongo Mayaye

Electrical Engineer

State Department of Public Works

P.O. Box 41194-00100,

Nairobi

Tel: 0716659322

2. Mr. George M. Mureithi

Chairman: Electrical and Electronics Engineering Department,

Kenyatta University.

P.O. Box 43844-00100,

Nairobi.

Tell: 810901-19

Email: chairman-electrical@ku.ac.ke

3. Eng. Silas Omondi

State Department of Public Works

P.O. Box 41194-00100,

Nairobi

Tel: 0720901684